So now that you have understand the concept of sectors and blocks, there is one more concept which
you have to know is related to Uid.
So as you know that each sector has 16.
Each Mifare classic card has 16 sectors and each sector has four blocks.
But blocks zero of sector zero is a special case which I am going to tell you right now.
So sector.
So.
Block zero of sector zero, the first four bytes.
Are the Uuid, right?
So the Uid, which we are using right now and which we used in our previous lectures is the which is
coming from the first four bytes of, of block zero of sector zero.
Right.
The other bytes in the in this block are the manufacturer data.
So these x x x are related to the manufacturer data.
So so the only thing which I need to tell you in this video is related to the Uid.
So the first four bytes in block zero of sector zero is Uid.